[horses galloping]
[TSAV] Isn't that...
[KIVIA] Humans!
[exclaims] Humans!
-[all clamoring]
-[MINER 1] Flaming arrows?
[MINER 2]
The barricade's on fire!
[horses neighing]
[Norgalle grunting]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[Xylo grunts] What the hell?
More transformed humans
akin to those in the mine?
No, far more complicated.
These scum have chosen
to side with the Demon Blight.
[TEORITTA] Truly?
Would that not imply
there are factions of faeries
capable of communicating
with humans?
[XYLO] That's right.
It's extremely rare,
but not unheard of.
[TEORITTA]
That does not bode well.
I am incapable
of attacking humans.
Even if they serve
the Demon Lord,
it is physically
impossible for me.
I'm aware.
Kivia! Come in now!
I'm here!
Your sacred-seal comms
are garbled with non-heroes.
Speak slowly!
Tell me what you know.
Who sent those
riders to fight us?
I don't have any idea.
Although...
I would wager they're some
noble family's private army
of horseback archers.
-[horse neighing]
-[KIVIA] Uh?
They're pulling back,
but we're too heavily armored
to give chase!
Dammit!
They're moving fast,
straight to the
underground passage!
[horses galloping, neighing]
[Venetim gasps]
[HOLY KNIGHT]
Something's coming.
Xylo, we need help here.
We're about to have
some company!
What should we do?
My life is in jeopardy!
If I perish, I'll never stop
haunting you!
You only ever care
about your own neck.
Venetim, you're fine,
so don't worry about it.
Tatsuya's got your back,
you're golden.
Majesty, we need to
get you off of the front lines.
We've got some kyracks incoming.
Retreat before
they breach the gate.
Nonsense!
Leave my men to fight
while their king cowers
in the face of danger?
[monsters growling]
[Norgalle grunting]
Chancellor, we need backup.
[Venetim sighs]
I'm afraid I can't accommodate
your request.
Besides...
you're not a king.
You have no authority.
[NORGALLE]
It seems we are on our own.
Do it! The embrasures!
[FOREMAN] Open the embrasures!
♪
What are those?
They're called runtels.
A type of
sacred-seal cannon
created by the
Verkle Development Corporation.
Prepare to fire!
[blows horn]
[MINER] Loaded and waiting!
Fire!
-[monster growling]
-[explosion]
Their aim leaves
much to be desired.
They'll have to reload.
We won't be ready
for the next wave.
[Norgalle grunts]
In that case,
it's up to you,
commander-in-chief!
Kill the general!
Should've known.
I'll handle our human foes.
Well? Are you ready?
Xylo.
Do you truly intend to do battle
no matter the outcome?
What are you getting at?
An observation.
You are constantly gambling
with your own life,
while discouraging me
from doing the same.
[footsteps]
[Xylo sighs]
[XYLO] I only take those risks
because they can
bring me back to life.
[TEORITTA] Liar.
You would still fight even
if that were not the case.
Do you have a point?
[TEORITTA]
Be it for the Holy Knights
and miners in the fortress,
or the nameless masses...
Your steady heart
never hesitates
to raise your sword for another.
Do you see, my knight?
You are no different
than a goddess.
In short, you claim to despise
our fundamental nature.
Because you see yourself
reflected in us.
♪
[Xylo grunts]
[Xylo sighs]
Dammit.
[monsters growling]
[XYLO] No time to waste.
Looks like the Demon Lord's
finally here.
Indeed. You are my hero
and I am your goddess.
It is imperative that I bless
the coming battle.
We have a sacred duty
that cannot be ignored.
There is no other choice,
knight.
[chuckles] Couldn't agree more.
Xylo...
To victory.
No excuses.
Right.
Let's go.
[horses neighing]
[holy knight 1 gasps]
[HOLY KNIGHT 2]
Are those humans?
Is this tunnel
to become all our graves?
[Venetim exclaims]
[Tatsuya grunts]
-[Tatsuya growling]
-What's he doing?
[Tatsuya inhales, yells]
[gasps]
-[MERCENARY 1] What the...
-[MERCENARY 2] What happened?
Stop! Ambu...
[Tatsuya yelling]
[gasps]
-[distant screaming]
-[knight whimpering]
[knights gasping]
[gasps] Hurry! Back him up!
Ready. Fire!
[all screaming]
[grunts]
[Tatsuya growls]
[mercenary gasping,
breathing shakily]
[MERCENARY] He's gone?
[screams]
[squelching]
[all breathing heavily]
[female holy knight gagging]
What the hell was that?
He can't be human.
[Tatsuya growls]
[RAJIT] That thing...
-is a demon.
-[Tatsuya screaming]
There...
That's Iblis.
[monster screeching]
Let's try to minimize combat.
We'll go around.
Understood.
My knight, you may proceed.
[XYLO] Perfect.
The plan is to stay alive!
Here we go!
♪
[Teoritta gasps]
[TEORITTA] Xylo!
[XYLO] Take that!
-[Teoritta gasps]
-[monster growls]
[Teoritta gasps]
A kyrack, eh?
Stay back! [grunts]
Teoritta, let's go!
[TEORITTA] Right!
[gasping]
It's a damn boggart?
[monster growls]
[Xylo screams]
Xylo! I shall summon
a rain of swords!
[XYLO] No!
I need you to save your power
for Iblis.
-I cannot stand idly...
-[monsters growling]
Damn it all to hell.
[growling]
[horses neighing]
[monsters growling]
[Xylo gasps]
[Xylo grunts]
[XYLO] Teoritta, hurry!
[monsters screeching]
What is that, my knight?
♪
-[Xylo grunts]
Venetim, explain yourself!
I told you to refuse their aid!
Right, I can only hope
you'll deign to forgive me.
[XYLO] In other words,
you lied to my face.
Honestly, you only have
yourself to blame.
What made you believe
I would be truthful
about something like that?
[Xylo sighs]
[DOTTA] Xylo!
I'm in big trouble!
If you don't help me,
I'm a goner!
Dotta? What the hell happened?
I'm being hunted down
by a band of mercenaries!
[XYLO] Why?
What did you do?
I sent you there
to hire those men!
[DOTTA] You also told me
to steal some money
to pay them.
Figured I'd kill two birds
with one stone
by paying them
with their own money!
Shut up! I get it!
Give us our money back,
you bastard!
We must charge the faerie horde!
[monster screeches]
[chuckles] They confused
the Demon Lord.
Guess that thing's even
stupider than I assumed.
Come on, let's fly.
It's time! Are you ready?
[TEORITTA] You need not ask!
[monster growling]
[Teoritta yelling]
[monster screaming]
[TEORITTA] I bestowed
upon this sword great size
and power to match.
It shall wither swiftly.
[XYLO] I know.
Just what I wanted.
My blessings
are glory incarnate,
are they not?
[Xylo gasps]
[TEORITTA] My knight?
[XYLO] Let's win this.
[Teoritta exclaims, chuckles]
Granted.
Ready.
-[monster growling]
-[Xylo scoffs]
Hurry up and face me!
[monster growling]
[Teoritta gasps]
[monster screeching]
[TEORITTA] Xylo, what happened?
[XYLO] It fell into the trap
I set while scouting.
Those are weathering seals.
-Teoritta!
-Behold!
Fell beast, we shall end you!
[TEORITTA]
These swords are certain
to endure
for quite some time.
[Teoritta grunts]
[yelling]
[monster groaning]
[yelling continues]
[Teoritta panting]
[XYLO] I'll tell Kivia's forces
to bring the goddess' poison.
Stay here and get some rest.
There wasn't
a single damn reason
for them to sacrifice
the fortress.
[monster screeching]
[XYLO] Look at it,
it doesn't have any fight left.
Now we can...
[Xylo gasps]
[Xylo grunts]
Teoritta!
Get away from here, now!
-[Teoritta gasps]
-[squelching]
[Teoritta grunts]
[TEORITTA] My brave knight.
[Teoritta gasps,
breathes shakily]
[monster growling]
[grunts] Listen, Teoritta...
[Teoritta gasps]
[XYLO] Run away.
[growling]
[Kivia grunts]
[KIVIA] Is this
the most we can do?
[NORGALLE] Loyal subjects,
retreat at once!
You've given
as much as you can.
Do it! Clear an escape route
for them, Tsav!
[TSAV] Not a chance!
We're in deep trouble here!
-Uh? Retreat!
-What the...
[TSAV] So can I run, too?
[Venetim pants] Please.
Whatever you do,
just don't come down here.
I need you
to hold them up there.
Wait a damn minute!
Who's gonna save me?
I'm being chased by
bloodthirsty mercenaries!
[mercenaries shouting]
[Xylo grunting]
Xylo, your wound.
Teoritta, go.
You have need of me.
[XYLO] Run away while
there aren't any faeries here.
[Xylo grunts]
I can tell that
you're at your limit.
It's as clear as day.
[Xylo grunting, coughing]
♪
[XYLO] You were right.
Everything you said is true.
You're a sick reflection
of myself.
We're the same.
I want to win a battle
that means something.
I want to prove my worth
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
I want to believe
I have something to offer
this twisted world.
It's a stupid,
selfish thing to want.
Even so...
I'm here.
This is my battle.
As you wish.
Regardless of your opinion
on the matter,
I shall remain
and fight by your side.
After all,
I am the peerless Teoritta,
your mighty goddess!
Of course.
How could I forget?
Xylo, if you desire
to see another day,
you need only protect
my life at all costs.
[monster growling]
[TEORITTA] I expect no less
from my valiant knight!
Understood.
I'm counting on you, Teoritta.
I'll be the one to decide
when you gamble your life.
Surely.
And when you die,
it will be on my order.
So it shall.
Then it's time, to victory!
[monster growling]
[TEORITTA] I shall prepare you
a special sword.
A truly magnificent blade.
[monster growling]
[XYLO] Can it slay an opponent
that's immortal?
[TEORITTA] Yes,
for this is the Holy Sword.
There is nothing
it cannot destroy.
I summon it here
from beyond this world.
Though short-lived,
it shall not break.
[Xylo chuckles softly]
[XYLO] Guess I'd better
make sure my strike lands true.
I won't falter.
[monster screeching]
[TEORITTA] Yes.
We shall never yield,
nor fail,
and nothing can break us!
[Xylo exclaims]
[Xylo grunting]
[screeching]
[Xylo grunting, yelling]
[Teoritta gasps]
[Xylo grunts]
Xylo!
[DOTTA] Xylo!
I lost the mercenaries!
What are you doing?
We gotta retreat!
[monster screeching]
[TSAV] Found you!
I was wondering
what happened
when you went
radio silent for a while.
All right,
here goes my last shot.
[monster screeches]
Teoritta!
Do it now!
[Teoritta yelling]
[Xylo yelling]
[Xylo grunting]
[grunts] Just die,
and rot in hell already!
[grunting]
[TEORITTA] Nothing exists...
that the one Holy Sword...
cannot destroy.
[Xylo gasps]
[Xylo breathes shakily]
[Teoritta breathes shakily]
[Teoritta groans]
[Teoritta chuckles]
Do you see?
Am I not truly great?
[Teoritta breathes shakily]
You are.
You sure as hell
proved yourself.
[footsteps]
[DOTTA] Xylo!
Teoritta's there with you,
right?
If you're hurt,
we'd better get you back fast!
[XYLO] It took you
long enough. [grunts]
-[thuds]
-[DOTTA] Xylo!
[Xylo grunts, groans]
[XYLO] Where am I?
[KAFZEN] Ah, the hero
finally awakens.
I do hope you're not
too uncomfortable, Xylo.
Who are you?
[KAFZEN] You can rest easy.
I'm pleased to report
you aren't dead just yet.
Although you were certainly
knocking upon death's door.
Your body has been restored
to a satisfactory condition.
You won't need
to visit the repair shop.
Of course, I can't guarantee
there won't be a minor amount
of memory loss.
I said, who are you?
[KAFZEN] Consider me an ally,
though, of course,
I can't force you to.
Either way,
I am relieved to see you
safe and sound.
After all, the hero unit
is our side's all-important
trump card.
Get lost.
Such cruel treatment.
I went to a lot of trouble
to speak with you.
It was quite difficult
to secure our privacy.
I even went out of my way
to deliver all your
little presents.
Simple tokens of gratitude
from the nearby settlements.
Seems you've earned
something of a reputation.
They call you
the "Soaring Lightning."
You heard me.
[Kafzen chuckles]
[KAFZEN] If you insist,
I will respect your wishes.
But there is something
you should know,
it isn't only the civilians.
Those in the Citadel
and the military
have also taken a keen notice
of what you heroes
have been up to--
Go away!
[Kafzen chuckles]
[KAFZEN] Oh, and one last thing.
Be careful not to violate
your orders too often.
There are some powerful people
out there who think of you
as a thorn in their side.
One faction in particular has
already set its sights on you.
I'm not surprised.
People call them
the "coexisters."
They seek harmony between humans
and the Demon Blight.
If you'll excuse me.
[swords clanking]
[Xylo grunting]
-[door opens]
-[KAFZEN] We are finished.
You are free
to enter now, goddess.
-[footsteps running]
-[TEORITTA] Xylo!
♪
Pray tell, my knight.
That lost gaze...
What does it mean?
I, your mighty goddess,
have chosen to bless your day
with the honor of my presence!
♪
I will be angry.
Take heed.
If you do not wish
to praise my efforts,
or pat me upon my head,
I accept that.
And yet,
of all sins...
The worst by far
is forgetting me.
I would never forgive you.
♪
[XYLO] I remember you, Teoritta.
So please...
don't cry.
[Teoritta sniffles]
[TEORITTA] I am not crying.
[XYLO] Of course not.
[TEORITTA] I am much
too great and powerful.
[XYLO] That, you are.